Finding Aid for Ivory Photo, Ann Arbor, Michigan ca. 1927-1971
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Negatives-- 4"x5"
  - University of Michigan
    - Alumni Activities
      - Fraternities
        - Dental (Xi Psi Phi) -- stone bench dedication February 10, 1939, 7 negatives (Box 15)
      - Memorabilia -- Gage Linen Shop 1948 (Box 15)
      - Reunions
        - Architecture
          - Class of 1924 1949, 2 negatives (Box 15)
          - Class of 1927 June 1947, 2 negatives (Box 15)
        - Business Administration
          - Class of 1934 1949 (Box 15)
          - Class of 1935 June 1950 (Box 15)
        - Class Officers' Banquet 1952 (Box 15)
        - Dental School
          - Class of 1899 1949 (Box 15)
          - Class of 1902 (Dean Russell Bunting) June 1947 (Box 15)
          - Class of 1913 1948 (Box 15)
          - Class of 1915
            - circa 1939 (Box 15)
            - circa 1960 (Box 15)
          - Class of 1917 June 1947 (Box 15)
          - Class of 1919 1949 (Box 15)
          - Class of 1924 1949 (Box 15)
          - Class of 1929 1949, 2 negatives (Box 15)
          - Class of 1933 1948 (Box 15)
          - Class of 1935 circa 1939 (Box 15)
          - Class of 1939 1949 (Box 15)
          - Class of 1945 June 1950 (Box 15)
          - Class of 1949 June 12, 1954 (Dr. Harry Bell), 2 negatives (Box 15)
          - Dedication of plaque circa 1940s (Box 15)
        - Engineering, College of
          - Class of 1904 January 1939 (Box 15)
          - Class of 1905 circa June 30, 1941 (Box 15)
          - Class of 1907 June 1947 (Box 15)
          - Class of 1913 1949 (Box 15)
          - Class of 1915 June 1950 (Box 15)
          - Class of 1930 1950 (Box 15)
          - Class of 1932 June 1947 (Box 15)
          - Class of 1940 June 1950 (Box 15)
        - Law School
          - Class of 1894 1949 (Box 15)
          - Class of 1895
            - June 1950 (Box 15)
            - 1952 (Box 15)
          - Class of 1900 circa 1950 (Box 15)
          - Class of 1904 1949 (Box 15)
          - Class of 1905 June 1950 (Box 15)
          - Class of 1914 1949 (Box 15)
          - Class of 1919 1949 (Box 15)
          - Class of 1925 June 1950 (Box 15)
          - Class of 1927 June 1947 (Box 15)
          - Class of 1935 June 1950 (Box 15)
          - Class of 1940 June 1950 (Box 15)
        - Literature and Engineering
          - Class of 1900 circa 1939, 3 negatives (Box 15)
          - Class of 1902 June 1947 (Box 15)
        - Literature, Science, and the Arts
          - Class of 1899 1949 (Box 15)
          - Class of 1905 1950 (Box 15)
          - Class of 1907 June 1947 (Box 15)
          - Class of 1910 1950 (Box 15)
          - Class of 1912 June 1947 (Box 15)
          - Class of 1917 June 1947 (Box 15)
          - Class of 1920 1950 (Box 15)
        - Medical School
          - Class of 1897 June 1947 (Box 15)
          - Class of 1901
            - June 1947 (Box 15)
            - 1949 (Box 15)
          - Class of 1905 June 1950 (Box 15)
          - Class of 1908 June 14, 1958 (Box 15)
          - Class of 1909 1949 (Box 15)
          - Class of 1912 1949 (Box 15)
          - Class of 1914 1949 (Box 15)
          - Class of 1919 1949 (Box 15)
          - Class of 1924 October 1950 (Box 15)
          - Class of 1925 circa 1939 (Box 15)
          - Class of 1929
            - circa 1939 (Box 15)
            - 1949, 2 negatives (Box 15)
          - Class of 1943 1948 (Box 15)
        - Music School June 3, 1948 (Box 15)
        - Pharmacy
          - Class of 1917 June 1947 (Box 15)
          - Class of 1937 June 1947 (Box 15)
        - Miscellaneous
          - Alumni Luncheon (Alexander Ruthven, Sam White, Mrs. Gilbreth) June 15, 1937, 2 negatives (Box 15)
          - August 10, 1937 (Box 15)
          - Davis and reunion anner 1937 (Box 15)
          - June 20 & 21 1941, 7 negatives (Box 15)
          - Luncheon -- Waterman Gym June 1947 (Box 15)
          - Class of 1937? (Sam Fiegel) October 1947 (Box 15)
          - Class of 1909 (Lit? Mr. Mertz) 1949 (Box 15)
    - Athletics
      - Badminton
        - IM Building April 10, 1939 (Box 15)
      - Baseball
        - 1930s (Oosterbaan), 2 negatives (Box 15)
        - May 1, 1937, 3 negatives (Box 15)
        - March 15, 1941, 3 negatives (Box 15)
        - 1948, 19 negatives (Box 15)
      - Basketball
        - John Townsend March 5, 1937, 2 negatives (Box 15)
        - Tom Harmon February 24, 1941, 3 negatives (Box 15)
        - Tom Harmon March 15, 1941 (Box 15)
        - Gordon Rosencranz December 20, 1945 (Box 15)
      - Bowling
        - Bowling trophy 1950 (Box 15)
      - Boxing
        - H. Wickers September 4, 1940, 2 negatives (Box 15)
        - March 15, 1941, 7 negatives (Box 15)
        - Coach Let Philbin and trophy winners May 1953, 3 negatives (Box 15)
        - Let Philbin and boxing champs March 31, 1954, 3 negatives (Box 15)
        - Let Philbin and trophy winners March 28, 1955, 3 negatives (Box 15)
        - Let Philbin, boxing team, and champs March 21, 1956, 2 negatives (Box 15)
        - Let Philbin with boxing team and champs March 25, 1957, 4 negatives (Box 15)
        - Let Philbin with boxing team and champs April 5, 1960, 3 negatives (Box 15)
        - Boxing squad with Let Philbin March 30, 1961, 3 negatives (Box 15)
        - Boxing team and coaches December 6, 1961, 4 negatives (Box 15)
        - Boxing team November 19, 1962, 5 negatives (Box 15)
        - Boxing squad with coach Let Philbin March 16, 1964, 3 negatives (Box 15)
      - Dance (women)
        - Palmer Field 1930s (Box 15)
      - Fencing
        - Intramural Open House March 14, 1940, 2 negatives (Box 15)
      - Field Hockey (women)
        - Palmer Field, late 1920s (Box 15)
        - U.S. Field Hockey Association teams November 1954, 18 negatives (Box 15)
      - Figure Skating (women's)
        - Womens figure skating March 15, 1941 (Box 15)
      - Football
        - Coaches
          - Crisler, Herbert O. ("Fritz")
            - With others February 14, 1938, 4 negatives (Box 15)
            - Mrs. Crisler and Scotty November 17, 1938, 2 negatives (Box 15)
            - Crisler and All-American candidates November 18, 1938, 7 negatives (Box 15)
            - Crisler in shower March 15, 1940 (Box 15)
            - October 3, 1940, 3 negatives (Box 15)
            - With players and others 1948, 2 negatives (Box 15)
            - With Boy Scout 1952 (Box 15)
          - Kipke, Harry
            - circa 1940 (Box 15)
            - at reunion, undated (Box 15)
          - Oosterbaan, Bennie
            - 1946, 2 negatives (Box 15)
            - June 1948, 3 negatives (Box 15)
          - Schembechler, Bo 1969, 2 negatives (Box 15)
          - Yost, Fielding
            - With Frank Murphy November 6, 1930 (Box 15)
            - With unidentified man circa 1930 (Box 15)
            - circa 1934, 2 negatives (Box 15)
            - With Charles Baird and Keene Fitzpatrick October 31, 1935, 4 negatives (Box 15)
            - With horn April 21, 1938, 4 negatives (Box 15)
            - Toast to Yost, Coast to Coast October 19, 1940
              - Stadium -- band formations and presentation, 5 negatives (Box 15)
              - Car presented to Yost by Fred Zeder, 2 negatives (Box 15)
              - Banquet, 11 negatives (Box 15)
            - With Mrs. Yost October 24, 1940, 2 negatives (Box 15)
            - Birthday banquet April 30, 1941, 4 negatives (Box 15)
            - In office October 6, 1941, 7 negatives (Box 15)
          - Miscellaneous (Crisler, Yost, and others) circa 1938 (Box 15)
        - Games and Practices
          - Football crowd at State and Packard 1929 (Box 15)
          - Harvard game send-off at Ann Arbor railroad station November 6, 1930, 8 negatives (Box 15)
          - Crowd and stadium scenes, cheerleaders, University of Chicago band 1930s, 11 negatives (Box 16)
          - Michigan 14 -- Michigan State College 19 October 2, 1937, 2 negatives (Box 16)
          - Michigan 6 -- Minnesota 39 October 16, 1937 (Box 16)
          - Michigan 7 -- Illinois 6 October 30, 1937, 6 negatives (Box 16)
          - Michigan 13 -- Chicago 12 November 6, 1937, 6 negatives (Box 16)
          - Pre-game riot in Ann Arbor -- Michigan-Michigan State October 1, 1938, 5 negatives (Box 16)
          - Michigan 45 -- Chicago 7 -- game and band October 8, 1938, 9 negatives (Box 16)
          - Send-off and return at depot for Minnesota game October 15, 1938, 5 negatives (Box 16)
          - Michigan 15 -- Yale 13 -- band formation October 22, 1938 (Box 16)
          - Michigan 14 -- Illinois 0(Tom Harmon, Pete Antonelli) October 29, 1938, 5 negatives (Box 16)
          - Michigan 19 -- Penn 3 November 12, 1938, 4 negatives (Box 16)
          - 1938 (Box 16)
          - Blocking September 13, 1939, 19 negatives (Box 16)
          - Caged wolverine; spectators, game October 7, 1939, 10 negatives plus Ivory notes (Box 16)
          - Michigan 27 -- Yale 6 -- Miss America and Jack Zubon; game, spectators October 28, 1939, 9 negatives (Box 16)
          - Minnesota 20 -- Michigan 7 November 11, 1939, 5 negatives (Box 16)
          - Michigan 24 -- Michigan State 14 -- Tom Harmon in action, spectators September 4, 1940, 6 negatives (Box 16)
          - Michigan 28 -- Illinois 0 October 19, 1940, 3 negatives (Box 16)
          - Michigan 14 -- Penn 0 October 26, 1940, 9 negatives (Box 16)
          - Michigan 20 -- Northwestern 13 November 6, 1940, 5 negatives (Box 16)
          - Michigan 40 -- Ohio 0 -- at Columbus -- Tom Harmon portrait and game November 23, 1940, 2 negatives (Box 16)
          - Fall circa 1940, 17 negatives (Box 16)
          - Michigan 6 -- Iowa 0 October 4, 1941, 3 negatives (Box 16)
            [see also similar print]
          - Michigan-Iowa November 28, 1942, 3 negatives (Box 16)
          - Michigan 9 -- Illinois 13 October 26, 1946, 5 negatives (Box 16)
          - Michigan 28 -- Wisconsin 6 November 16, 1946, 4 negatives (Box 16)
          - Michigan 49 -- Stanford 13 October 4, 1947, 2 negatives (Box 16)
          - Michigan 69 -- Pittsburgh 0 October 11, 1947, 7 negatives (Box 16)
          - Michigan 14 -- Oregon 0 October 2, 1948, 4 negatives (Box 16)
          - 1948
            - Michigan 54 -- Indiana 0, 4 negatives (Box 16)
            - Michigan 28 -- Illinois 20, 6 negatives (Box 16)
            - Michigan 28 -- Northwestern 0, 4 negatives (Box 16)
            - Michigan 35 -- Navy 0, 2 negatives (Box 16)
          - 1949
            - Michigan 7 -- Michigan State 3, 6 negatives (Box 16)
            - Michigan 20 -- Purdue 12, 6 negatives (Box 16)
            - Michigan 20 -- Indiana 7, 6 negatives (Box 16)
            - Michigan 14 -- Minnesota 7, 3 negatives (Box 16)
            - Michigan 7 -- Ohio State 7, 6 negatives (Box 16)
            - Army 21 -- Michigan 7, 5 negatives (Box 16)
          - Michigan 27 -- Dartmouth 7 October 7, 1950, 6 negatives (Box 16)
          - Michigan 0 -- Illinois 7 November 4, 1950, 2 negatives (Box 16)
          - Michigan 20 -- Indiana 7 November 11, 1950 game, cheerleaders, 8 negatives (Box 16)
          - Michigan 26 -- Wisconsin 13 1950, 4 negatives (Box 16)
          - Michigan 34 -- Northwestern 23 1950, 6 negatives (Box 16)
        - Team Members
          - Simrall circa 1930 (Box 16)
          - Fred Janke March 15, 1936 (Box 16)
          - Janke and Ingalls April 3, 1939 (Box 16)
          - Paul Nielson October 14, 1939, 2 negatives (Box 16)
          - Tom Harmon October 17, 1939, 7 negatives (Box 16)
          - Tom Harmon, Forest Evashevski (in dormitory?) October 31, 1939, 4 negatives (Box 16)
          - Tom Harmon with friends, on campus October 2, 1940, 5 negatives (Box 16)
          - Tom Harmon with Bob Hawks; Tom Harmon getting hair cut by Leo Lirette October 21, 1940, 3 negatives (Box 16)
          - Julius Franks October 25, 1940 (Box 16)
          - Tom Harmon and Bill Stern in radio broadcasting studio October 26, 1940, 2 negatives (Box 16)
          - Tom Harmon -- WJR broadcast 1940 (Box 16)
          - Tom Harmon's parents, Tom Harmon with date circa 1940, 4 negatives (Box 16)
          - Tom Harmon March 15, 1941 (Box 16)
          - Tom Harmon and Anita Louise June 20, 1941, 10 negatives (Box 16)
          - Tom Kuzma with Peggy Cannon and playing football October 21, 1941, 5 negatives (Box 16)
          - Lloyd Heneveld, Robert Van Summern, Ralph Kohl, Robert Erben, Quentin Sickels, Tom Peterson, Dan Dworsky, Bob Hallway, and others June 17, 1948, 12 negatives (Box 16)
          - 1948
            - Frosh Squad (Box 16)
            - 150-pound squad, 2 negatives (Box 16)
          - Frosh Squad 1949 (Box 16)
          - Frosh Squad 1950 (Box 16)
          - Jack Clancy August 11, 1966, 2 negatives (Box 16)
        - Miscellaneous
          - Wolverines -- Detroit Zoo 1938 (Box 17)
          - M-Men -- Old Timers October 22, 1939, 6 negatives (Box 17)
          - Henry Hatch and famous football jerseys October 29, 1940 (Box 17)
          - Little Brown Jug 1948, 2 negatives (Box 17)
          - Chevrolet Motor Division prize ceremony November 12, 1949, 6 negatives (Box 17)
          - "Sorry Mr. Zuppke" sign -- Michigan vs. Illinois circa 1940s (Box 17)
          - Father McPhillips -- mass for team October 27, 1951 (Box 17)
      - Golf
        - Frosh team April 15, 1939, 5 negatives (Box 17)
        - Team 1948, 11 negatives (Box 17)
      - Hockey team December 13, 1945, 3 negatives (Box 17)
    - Athletics
      - Horse shows
        - May 29, 1931, 4 negatives (Box 17)
        - March 15, 1941 (Box 17)
      - Intramural Sports
        - Open House -- staff, hockey, badminton, ping pong, volleyball, basketball, wrestling March 12, 1939, 8 negatives (Box 17)
        - Open House -- staff March 14, 1940 (Box 17)
        - Newt Loken group 1949 (Box 17)
        - Les Etter luncheon circa 1949, 11 negatives (Box 17)
        - Earl Riskey groups 1951-1956, 10 negatives (Box 17)
        - Trophies 1957 (Box 17)
        - Interscholastic Team with Coach Keen March 15, 1958, 2 negatives (Box 17)
        - Earl Riskey groups 1958-1961, 3 negatives (Box 17)
      - Michigan Managers Club
        - Group Photo October 12, 1946, 2 negatives (Box 17)
      - Paddleball
        - Earl Riskey and paddleball champs circa 1952 (Box 17)
        - Champs January 1965, 8 negatives (Box 17)
      - Sailing
        - March 15, 1941 (Box 17)
      - Speedboat Racing
        - March 15, 1941, 2 negatives (Box 17)
      - Swimming
        - circa 1930s, 2 negatives (Box 17)
        - Coach Matt Mann March 1, 1931, 3 negatives (Box 17)
        - U-M swimmers (men and women) at Detroit Athletic Club March 1, 1938, 13 negatives (Box 17)
        - May 4, 1938
          - Matt Mann's swimming class, 8 negatives (Box 17)
          - Palmer diving, 4 negatives (Box 17)
        - Swimming team -- Captain Tom Haynie and Waldemar Tomoki February 14, 1939, 4 negatives (Box 17)
        - Michigan-Yale swim meet -- swimmers and spectators February 20, 1939, 6 negatives (Box 17)
        - Diver March 1, 1939 (Box 17)
        - National Collegiate Athletic Association swim meet (Jim Kiefer, Jim Welsh), March 24 & 25 1939, 7 negatives (Box 17)
        - June 12, 1939
          - Tom Haynie and Matt Mann, 6 negatives (Box 17)
          - Irene Burke and other women swimmers, 20 negatives (Box 17)
        - March 15, 1941, 3 negatives (Box 17)
      - Tennis
        - Coach LeRoy Weir July 28, 1937, 2 negatives (Box 17)
        - Gordon McLeod October 1, 1937, 3 negatives (Box 17)
        - Men and women March 15, 1941, 10 negatives (Box 17)
        - 1948, 3 negatives (Box 17)
      - Track and Field
        - May 1, 1937, 4 negatives (Box 17)
        - Track meet October 12, 1939, 3 negatives (Box 17)
        - circa 1940
          - Runner, 2 negatives (Box 17)
          - Coach Stackhouse and team, 3 negatives (Box 17)
        - Runners, shot putter, pole vaulter, high jumper March 15, 1941, 22 negatives (Box 17)
      - Volleyball
        - foreign students? (Earl Riskey) December 7, 1955, 8 negatives (Box 17)
      - Women's Golf
        - March 15, 1941, 2 negatives (Box 17)
      - Wrestling
        - Squad members December 11, 1945, 9 negatives (Box 17)
        - Squad members March 31, 1957, 2 negatives (Box 17)
    - Buildings and Views
      - Administration Building 1949 (Box 17 A)
      - Aerial Views
        - The Mall: Rackham to Natural Sciences circa 1935 (Box 17 A)
        - Rackham and environs July 14, 1938, 3 negatives (Box 17 A)
        - circa 1938 (Box 17 A)
        - October 12, 1939, 4 negatives (Box 17 A)
      - Alumni Memorial Hall
        - Fall 1930, 3 negatives (Box 17 A)
        - Exterior circa 1930 (Box 17 A)
        - Interior circa 1935 (Box 17 A)
        - circa 1946 (Box 17 A)
        - with Alumni Association banner, undated (Box 17 A)
      - Angell Hall
        - circa 1928-1930 (Box 17 A)
        - late 1920s/early 1930s, 3 negatives (Box 17 A)
        - circa 1930 (Box 17 A)
        - Fall 1930 (with Newberry Hall) (Box 17 A)
        - Summer 1937, 2 negatives (Box 17 A)
        - circa 1938 (Box 17 A)
          [see also 5"x7" negatives]
        - Goldcamp's Pillars January 11, 1938 (Box 17 A)
        - Hopwood Room July 15, 1939, 3 negatives (Box 17 A)
      - Arboretum
        - Peony Garden circa 1930 (Box 17 A)
        - circa 1930, 2 negatives (Box 17 A)
          (one photo shot from gas station across the street)
        - Peony Garden circa 1930-1935 (Box 17 A)
        - Peonies June 14, 1937, 2 negatives (Box 17 A)
        - July 27, 1937 (Box 17 A)
        - December 27, 1945, 2 negatives (Box 17 A)
      - Architecture Building (Lorch Hal)
        - Fall 1930 (Box 17 A)
        - circa 1930, 4 negatives (Box 17 A)
        - circa 1930 Architectural fragments, 6 negatives (Box 17 A)
        - September 12, 1935 (Box 17 A)
        - March 14, 1937, 2 negatives (Box 17 A)
        - July 27, 1937 (Box 17 A)
        - Summer 1937 (Box 17 A)
        - circa 1946 (Box 17 A)
        - September 23, 1965, 4 negatives (Box 17 A)
      - Athletic Administration Building July 27, 1937, 2 negatives (Box 17 A)
      - Automotive Laboratory. (Box 17 A)
        (See: West Engineering Annex)
      - Baird Carillon. (Box 17 A)
        (See: Burton Tower)
      - Barbour (Betsy) Dormitory
        - Fall 1930 (Box 17 A)
        - circa 1930, 2 negatives (Box 17 A)
        - May 22, 1935 (Box 17 A)
        - 1937 (Box 17 A)
      - Burton Tower
        - Under construction November 17, 1936, 2 negatives (Box 17 A)
        - Hanging bells December 2, 1936, 5 negatives (Box 17 A)
        - Presentation of bell, Baird Carillon December 1936 (Box 17 A)
        - Baird Carillon (Wayne Hartwell) January 27, 1937, 7 negatives (Box 17 A)
        - Bell tower and North University February 16, 1937, 3 negatives (Box 17 A)
        - Under construction March 17, 1937 (Box 17 A)
        - At night April 12, 1937, 6 negatives (Box 17 A)
        - June 30, 1937, 3 photographs (Box 17 A)
        - Plaque and stone work July 10, 1937 (Box 17 A)
          [6 negatives]
        - August 20, 1937, 2 negatives (Box 17 A)
        - Summer 1937 (Box 17 A)
        - January 5, 1940 (Box 17 A)
        - March 22, 1940, 2 negatives (Box 17 A)
        - 1957 (Box 17 A)
      - Business Administration 1949, 3 negatives (Box 18)
      - Campus Scenes
        - Students circa 1929 (Box 18)
        - Students and dogs on diag and other walks, water fountain, streets and buildings 1930s, 21 negatives (Box 18)
        - Construction near Betsy Barbour March 31, 1931 (Box 18)
        - Magazine salesman in Nickels Arcade June 1932 (Box 18)
        - Campus walk May 22, 1935 (Box 18)
        - "Mall" -- Rackham and Burton Tower June 27, 1938 (Box 18)
        - Winter scene 1938, 2 negatives (Box 18)
        - circa 1940
          - Construction, 2 negatives (Box 18)
          - Glider and students (Box 18)
          - Cooley fountain and Rackham (Box 18)
        - Cooley fountain July 23, 1941, 2 negatives (Box 18)
        - 1947
          - Construction -- East Quadrangle addition, Food Service Building, Veterans' Readjustment Center, Women's residence hall, 4 negatives (Box 18)
          - Quonset huts (Box 18)
      - Chemical Laboratory Building, Summer 1937 (Box 18)
      - Chemistry Building circa 1930 (Box 18)
      - Children's Institute
        - October 24, 1940, 3 negatives (Box 18)
        - 1953 (Box 18)
      - Clements Library
        (See also: UM Buildings and Views -- Engineering -- West Engineering Annex (late 1920s))
        - circa 1930, 6 negatives (Box 18)
        - women in blue Room circa 1932, 2 negatives (Box 18)
        - March 4, 1937, 2 negatives (Box 18)
      - Cook (Martha) Dormitory
        - circa 1930, 3 negatives (Box 18)
        - Summer 1937 (Box 18)
        - Twenty-fifth Anniversary Tea -- group photos including Alexander Ruthven October 12, 1940, 10 negatives (Box 18)
      - Couzens Hall (dormitory) July 27, 1937, 2 negatives (Box 18)
      - Dental Building
        - circa 1930, 5 negatives (Box 18)
        - February 20, 1938, 2 negatives (Box 18)
        - Kellogg Institute and Health Service Building, Fall 1945 (Box 18)
        - Kellogg Institute, undated (Box 18)
      - East Quad (Men's dormitory)
        - October 6, 1940, 7 negatives (Box 18)
        - 1949, 2 negatives (Box 18)
      - Economics Building, late 1920s-early 1930s (Box 18)
      - Engineering
        - East Engineering
          - May 7, 1935 (Box 18)
          - June 10, 1937, 2 negatives (Box 18)
        - East Hall, late 1920s (Box 18)
        - Engineering Research Institute 1952, 2 negatives (Box 18)
        - West Engineering
          - Engineering Arch circa 1930 (Box 18)
          - Minaret May 23, 1935 (Box 18)
          - Minarets January 30, 1937 (Box 18)
        - West Engineering Annex
          - With Clements Library, late 1920s (Box 18)
          - With clock tower August 30, 1935 (Box 18)
          - With clock tower July 2, 1940, 3 negatives (Box 18)
      - Ferry Field Gate
        - circa 1930 (Box 18)
        - July 27, 1937, 2 negatives (Box 18)
      - Fountains. (Box 18)
        (See: Campus Scenes)
      - Fraternities and Sororities
        - Alpha Delta Pi. (Box 18)
          (See: Ann Arbor -- Buildings and Views -- Houses and Businesses -- 722 South Forest)
        - Alpha Gamma Delta (1322 Hill Street) circa September 1954, 2 negatives (Box 18)
        - Alpha Phi (1830 Hill Street)
          - circa 1957, 2 negatives (Box 18)
          - Interiors October 31, 1963, 3 negatives (Box 18)
        - Alpha Tau Omega. (Box 18)
          (v)
        - Beta Theta Pi (604 South State Street) circa 1960s (Box 18)
          [see also 5"x7" negatives
        - Delta Gamma. (Box 18)
          (See: Ann Arbor Buildings and Views -- Houses and Businesses -- 1205 Hill Street)
        - Delta Kappa Epsilon (William Street) circa 1930s (Box 18)
        - Kappa Alpha Theta (Washtenaw Avenue) 1947 (Box 18)
        - Kappa Kappa Gamma circa 1940 (Box 18)
        - Phi Beta Pi (1010 East Ann Street) circa 1943 (Box 18)
        - Phi Gamma Delta (707 Oxford) circa 1960 (Box 18)
        - Pi Beta Phi (836 Tappan). (Box 18)
        - Psi Omega. (Box 18)
          (See: Ann Arbor Buildings and Views -- Houses and Businesses -- 2031 Hill Street)
        - Sigma Alpha Mu. (Box 18)
          (See: Ann Arbor Buildings and Views -- Houses and Businesses -- 800 Lincoln)
        - Theta Delta Chi. (Box 18)
        - unidentified November 20, 1930 (Box 18)
      - Frieze
        - circa 1957, 2 negatives (Box 18)
        - February 1958, 2 negatives (Box 18)
      - Golf Course
        - late 1920s, 2 negatives (Box 18)
        - circa 1930 (Box 18)
        - October 25, 1938 (Box 18)
        - September 11, 1939 aerial photos, 3 negatives (Box 18)